RAHULIA KRISTANTI

(+62) 8953-2241-7891 | rahuliakristanti08@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/rahulia-kristanti | Portfolio Semarang, Central Java, 50254

SUMMARY

A associate degree of Telecommunication Technology from Universitas Telkom. Experienced as a practium assistant as well as familiar with installation software, hardware, and troubleshooting. Currently attending a bootcamp for deepering skills in full stack web developer. A hardworking person who is open to full time work opportunities to develop a career in IT field and web development.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Lab Cellcom Universitas Telkom – Bandung, Indonesia

Practicum Assistant (September 2023 – November 2023)

 Assisting 60 telecommunication technology students to do their practicum task at the mobile communication system course using Atoll and G-NetTrack

PT. Dirgantara Indonesia – Bandung, Indonesia

Aircraft Electrician at Divisi Electrical Sub Assembly (March 2023 – June 2023)

- Handled the varnishing process of 2 critical components that had been assembled
- Performed continuity tests on the AFCS system using NI PXIe-1065, LabVIEW, and TestStand to ensure that the components were functioning properly

Lab RLK (Electrical Circuit) - Bandung, Indonesia

Practicum Assistant (July 2021 - December 2022)

Assisting 100 telecommunication technology students to do their practicum task at the electrical circuit course
using hardware such as a multimeter to calculate the magnitude of electric current, voltage, and resistance, as well
as several software programs such as Multisim and Proteus

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES

Himpunan Mahasiswa D3 Teknologi Telekomunikasi – Bandung, Indonesia

Staff of Ristek Department (March 2021 – December 2022)

Success to perform webinar with alumni of Telecommunication Technology with 100 participants

Formasi (Forum Mahasiswa Penerima Beasiswa KIP-K) - Bandung, Indonesia

Coordinator of PSDM Division (April 2022 - March 2023)

- Lead 6 members to plan and do some work program such as Upgrading and Formasi Responsi
- Success to perform webinar with national level speaker like Vina Muliana with 1000 participants

EDUCATION

Universitas Telkom - Bandung, Indonesia

D-3 Telecommunication Technology – GPA 3.93 / 4.00 (August 2020 – October 2023)

Relevant Subjects: Programming Workshop I; Programming Workshop II

COURSES, TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

Harisenin.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

Bootcamp in Full Stack Web Developer

- Projects Basic Mission: Create 1 simple MVP landing page consisting of only 1 page using HTML and CSS. Link: <u>rahuliakristanti.github.io/roomify-landing-page/</u>
- Relevant Courseworks: Introduction to Software Engineer, HTML, and CSS

SKILLS & ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Hard skills: Assisting, trouleshooting, software, hardware, Ms Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python
- Soft skills: Communication, analytical thinking, problem solving, curiosity
- Language: Bahasa (Native), English (Intermediate; EprT Score: 480)